(Sheldon:)I sense you're making a joke,
but Bozeman does have...
(Sheldon:)...a comedy club called the Loony Bin,
so do not forward my mail there.
(Howard:)Oh, come on. So you were the victim
of a crime. That's part of life.
(Howard:)When my great-grandfather
first came to this country...
(Howard:)...he put all his hopes and dreams
into this little butcher shop...
(Howard:)...he ran on the Lower East Side
of New York. You know what happened?
(Howard:)Every customer who
walked into that butcher shop...
(Howard:)...and asked for a pound of liver...
[SNAPS FINGERS]
(Howard:)...got ripped off.
(Howard:)But those people moved on,
and so should you.
(Sheldon:)I am moving on.
I'm going to be a Bozite.
(Leonard:)They call themselves Bozites?
(Sheldon:)They should. It's one of the first things
I plan to bring up upon arrival.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I'm gonna miss you.
(Sheldon:)Please, Penny. As you know, I'm not
comfortable with prolonged goodbyes...
(Sheldon:)...and maudlin displays of emotion,
so I've prepared a short video.